const questions = [
        { 
                question: "This is the mock for question1",
                clue1: "Answer is answer1",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer1"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question2",
                clue1: "Answer is answer2",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer2"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question3",
                clue1: "Answer is answer3",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer3"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question4",
                clue1: "Answer is answer4",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer4"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question5",
                clue1: "Answer is answer5",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer5"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question6",
                clue1: "Answer is answer6",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer6"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question7",
                clue1: "Answer is answer7",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer7"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question8",
                clue1: "Answer is answer8",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer8"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question9",
                clue1: "Answer is answer9",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer9"
        },
        {
                question: "This is the mock for question10",
                clue1: "Answer is answer10",
                clue2: null,
                answer: "answer10"
        }
];

module.exports = { questions };